Business Ephemera Collection
Hartford History Center, Hartford Public Library
- Trade cards, Business Cards, Miscellaneous Small Advertisements
  - Trade card, A.T. Leonard, 187-?; Three different floral designs (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Trade card, Leach and Kingsbury, 1868?; Dealers in Pharmaceutical Preparations, Toilet Articles, Wines for Medicinal Use, Mineral Waters, Etc. (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Trade card, A.T. Leonard, 187-?; Three different floral designs (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Postcard, Charles H. Leppert, 1922?; "Motor repairs delivered when Promised. Used Motors Bought Sold and Rented. Industrial Electrical Repairs." (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Trade card, Lester and Collard, 18--?; Two different floral designs (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Trade card, Henry Lewis and Company, 186-?; "Ensign's Old Stand." Proprietors are Henry Lewis and John Alexander. (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Business card, Literacy Volunteers of Connecticut, 1977; Business card of Julie Stone, Director (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Postcard, Long's Cabaret, 1915?; Performers include George Wright, James Finley, John Mackey, Jack Barry, and Jack Russell. (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Business card, Mrs. H. Loomis, 1856?; "First-Class Help Furnished, Both Male and Female…." (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Trade card, Loomis and Whittlesey, 185-?; "Choice Butter and Fresh Eggs a Specialty." (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Trade card, Lovell, Tracy and Company, 189-?; "Climax Mowing Machine Oil, for Mowers, Threshers, Reapers, &c., Little Giant Lubricator for Lawn Mowers, Fine Engine Oils, Light and Dark Axle Oils, Harness Oil." (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Trade card, Lovell, Tracy and Company, 1892?; Partners are C. A. Lovell and S. G. Tracy. Successors to C. A. Lovell and Company. (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Trade card, Ludlow Barker and Company, 1876; Image depicts the Main Exhibition Building at the 1876 International Exhibition in Philadelphia. (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Business card, Luettgens Limited, 199-?; View of Hartford skyline (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Postcard, Lux Bond and Green, 1993; Postcard advertising an exhibition of Limoges Boxes at store in West Hartford (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Advertisement, Lux Bond and Green, 198-?; Advertisement on back of Bushnell Memorial Hall ticket envelope (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Business card, Lux Bond and Green, 1990?; Business card of Lana Tan Lee (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Trade card, Lynn's Concert Rooms, 189-?; "Established 1841. Incorporated 1879. Telephone 21-2." (Box 9, Folder L)
  - Trade card, H. Maercklein, 1877?; "Inventor and Manufacturer of the 'Simplicity' Sofa and Lounge Bed." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, Mammoth Bargain Store, 188-?; One card depicting a boy with a basket and a flowering branch (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, Mansuy Carriage Manufacturing Company, 189-?; "Established 1841. Incorporated 1879. Telephone 21-2." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Business card, Manzi's of Hartford, 1978?; Business card of Raymond J. Manzi. "Catering with Elegance." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, Marcy and Haynes, 187-?; Partners are F. A. Marcy and C. W. Haynes (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Postcard, H.C. Marquardt, 192-?; "Money to Loan on First and Second Mortgages in Sums and Terms to Suit Patrons." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Postcard, A. Marwick, Jr. and Company, 188-?; "Nearest Drug Store to Union Depot." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, Charles B. May, 185-?; "Will furnish Newells, Balusters, Screws, and Rails wrought and un-wrought of the different kinds of wood and send to any part of the country." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, David Mayer, 187-?; Three different designs featuring birds (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, David Mayer, 187-?; Design featuring a girl with a doll and wagon (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, L. Mayer, 188-?; Printed by Clay & Richmond, Buffalo, N.Y. (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Envelopes, John McClary, 1893; Envelopes postmarked 1893 (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, McClunie Brothers, 187-?; Four floral designs (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, McClunie Brothers, 190-?; Four different designs, one advertising "Singing, Talking, and Fancy Birds." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Business card, William J. McConville, 190-?; "With H. S. and S. Barbour." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, George M. McCorkle, 189-?; Advertisement for "Rubifoam for the Teeth." Design copyrighted 1890. (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, John McCullough, 188-?; "Custom Shirts to Order a Specialty." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, Miss Alie McQuillan, 190-?; "Gray Hair A Specialty." "Ladies' and Children's Bang Cutting, Curling, and Shampooing." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Postcard, Thomas McRonald, ca. 1900; Postcard with poem: "Make your home beautiful, bring to it flowers…." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Business card, Fred Mertz, Jr., Inc., ca. 1900; Business card of Fred Mertz, Jr. (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, W.C. Messinger, 1881?; Advertisements for Pond's Extract products on front and back of card (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Postcard, R.G. Miller and Sons, 192-?; Card lists recipes for "Cool… Creamy… Delicious… Desserts" using heavy cream (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, William G. Miller, 187-?; Carte-de-visite with photograph of 403-407 Main Street; also includes advertising for T. Steele and Son, Importers and Jewelers. (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Business card, Miner and Griswold, 186-?; Business card of H. E. Mather "Formerly at 468 Main Street." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, Misfit Parlors, 188-?; Seventeen different designs (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Business card, Frank A. Mitchell, 189-?; "Lately Injured on the Railroad." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Business card, A. Moeller, 1875; Receipt on verso dated January 18th 1875. (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Business card, A. Moeller, 1897; Receipt on verso dated February 12, 1897 (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, E.H. Moody, 18--?; "Formerly of Fisk and Moody." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, N.K. Morgan, 189-?; "Delicious and Fragrant Tassa Cures Sore Throats in 3 or 4 Hours, Prevents Dipththeria, and all Throat Troubles such as Bronchitis, Hoarseness, Loss of Voice, Tickling of Throat, Sudden Colds, &C. &c. and for the relief of Consumption." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, S.G. Moses and Company, 187-?; Printed by Bufford, Boston. (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, Motorette, 1911?; Card shows man and woman in motorette in mountains. In 1911 a motorette took part in a cross-country race. (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Label, Curtis H. Moyer, 190?; Label inscribed "Tower of Phillip LaBell / Port St. Andre / Avignon." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Postcard, Moyer Gallery, 193-?; "Gifts for the Year 'Round Bazaar Francais Copper." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Postcard, Moyer Gallery, 193-?; "Gifts for the Year 'Round Bazaar Francais Copper." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Postcard, Moyer Gift Gallery, 194-?; Proprietor is listed as Paul W. Cooley, who took over the business in 1938. (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, Mulcahy the Outfitter, 189-?; "Klothing, Hats, Trunks and Furnishings." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Trade card, Mulcahy's Boston One Price Clothing House, 188-?; "Blue Store. Custom Tailoring a Specialty. All Goods Can be Returned if not Soiled and Money Cheerfully Refunded. Look for the Blue Building." (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Business card, Municipal Cafeteria, 198-?; "Established 1924." Business card of Elise McKay, Catering Coordinator. (Box 9, Folder M)
  - Business card, John Naedele, 18--?; "Wine & Lager Beer." "A Few Blocks from State Street." (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Business card, National Puerto Rican Forum, 199-?; Business card of Mildred Lopez-Cook, B.C.S.T. Coordinator (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Business card, Neighborhood Legal Services, Inc., 198-?; Business card of Emma E. Lopez and two other business cards (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Trade card, Nelson's Busy Drug Store, 192-?; "Headquarters for Trusses, Abdominal Supports, Elastic Stockings, Anklets, Knee Caps, Etc." (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Trade card, New England Boot and Shoe House, 188-?; Four different designs (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Trade card, New England Boot and Shoe House, 188-?; "Compliments of J. Samuels & Co.'s New England Boot and Shoe House." (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Trade card, New England Boot and Shoe House, 188-?; "Compliments of E. A. Perry." Three different designs featuring couples (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Business card, New England Farm Workers Council, 198-?; Business card of Ana Gomez, Employment Developer and Job Developer (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Trade card, New England One Price Boot and Shoe House, 1876?; Partners are Hirschberg and Samuels (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Postcard, New England Water Works Association, 1917; "Annual Convention--Hartford, Sept. 11 to 15… Special Feature---All day automobile trip over Hartford's New Supply Works… " (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Trade card, New York Dining Rooms, 18--?; "Hot Meals, 25c. Ice Cream all Flavors." (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Trade card, New York 25 Ct. Store, 18--?; Two different designs (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Trade card, Nicoll the Tailor, 187-?; Two different designs printed by Charles Shields Sons, New York (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Trade card, Nicoll the Tailor, 187-?; Two different designs printed by Charles Shields Sons, New York (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Trade card, Nicoll the Tailor, 187-?; Five humorous designs (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Trade card, Nicoll the Tailor, 188-?; One humorous design featuring a large man on a small polo pony (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Trade card, Nicoll the Tailor, 188-?; Three designs illustrating "Jack and Jill," printed by Charles Shields Sons, New York (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Trade card, Nicoll the Tailor, 187-?; Eleven miscellaneous designs (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Trade card, Nilson and Murray, 186-?; "Oysters delivered to any part of the city free of charge." (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Trade card, S.C. Northrop, 187-?; Advertisement on back of carte-de-visite photograph of a woman: "We also present free of charge with each and every Dollar's worth of goods bought of us, an elegant Chromo, Engraving or Lithorgraph, which retails from 50 Cents to $1.50." (Box 10, Folder N)
  - Business card, Old State House, 198-?; Business card of Karen Bass (Box 10, Folder O)
  - Trade card, Original New England Tea, Coffee and Spice Establishment, 186-?; Also "Cocoa, Chocolate, Broma, &c." (Box 10, Folder O)
  - Trade card, J.H. Otis, 188-?; "One Price to all, and that lower than any House in the City." Six floral designs. (Box 10, Folder O)
  - Trade card, J.H. Otis, 188-?; Two different designs (Box 10, Folder O)
  - Trade card, J.H. Otis, 188-?; One Oriental design (Box 10, Folder O)
  - Trade card, J.H. Otis, 188-?; "Tickets Free to the Circus to Everyone who Purchases Clothing to the Amount of $10.00." (Box 10, Folder O)
  - Trade card, J.H. Otis, 188-?; "Line of March. At 11:30 a National Salute will be fired…." (Box 10, Folder O)
  - Postcard, Packard Motor Car Company, 1954; Joseph J. Hills, Proprietor. "It's new thru and thru! The Packard '200' Touring Sedan offers new low-to-the-road styling… " (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Business card, Paper Chase, 1984; Philip A. Pizzanello, President. "A New Kind of Office Supply Store." (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Business card, Parents Anonymous of Connecticut, 199-?; Business card of Leelaine Picker. "Because Love Doesn't Have to Hurt." (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Blotter, Paris Shoe Rebuilding Company, 193-?; "We can put on soles that stand up under the roughest kind of romping." (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, Park Central Hotel, 188-?; W. Ketchum, Proprietor. Note on back: "Park Central blown to pieces Feb 18, 1889. / Monday morning." (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, Parker and Kellogg, 18--?; Card in the shape of an artist's pallette. "The White Sewing Machine / The Best in the World." (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Postcard, James A. Parsons, 192-?; "What appear to be calamities are often the sources of fortune." (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Postcard, Parsons' Theatre, 1910; "The Hunter-Bradford Players to present J. M. Barrie's sweetest comedy 'The Little Minister.'" (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, M.W. Pember and Company, 187-?; One design featuring monkeys (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, M.W. Pember and Company, 187-?; Three designs featuring dogs and birds (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, V.D. Perry, 188-?; One comic design with Perry's name and address added using a rubber stamp (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, Lew Pierson's Black and White Studio, 192-?; "Pen - Brush & Crayon." 2 copies of same card. (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, J.F. Pitkin, 18--?; Three different floral designs (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, W.L. and H.E. Pitkin, 187-?; "Hollow Ware of Every Description. Also, Jobbing in Gold and Silver Plating." (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, W.S. Pitkin, 1868?; "With F. M. Warren" (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, Pitkin Bothers and Company Iron Works, 189-?; Manuscript notes with prices of engines and boilers on back. (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Business card, Plaza Market and Deli, 198-? (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, George W. Pomroy, 1889?; "The Pomroy Handy Wagon. The Best Wagon in the World for the Money." (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, Pomroy, 18--?; "This Man bought a Carriage of Pomroy… Sold by Geo. H. Olmsted, Jr." (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, Joseph Pomroy, 186-?; "Choice Green and Black Teas, Choice Wines and Liquors, Imported and Domestic Cigars." (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Bookmark, Pond and Childs, 187-?; One Oriental design. (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Business card, Bill Posey, 1985?; Business card with picture of Posey as Mark Twain (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, William H. Post and Company, 188-?; William H. Post, E. S. Yergason, Proprietors. "Artistic and Modern House Furnishings A Specialty." (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, Pratt Street House, 189-?; C. V. Chapin, Manager. "First Class Accommodations for Regular and Transient Boarders. Special Rates for Commercial Travelers." (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Postcard, Pratt and Cady Company, 1888; R. N. Pratt, President; Ernest Cady, Secretary and Treasurer (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, Charles S. Pratt, 188-?; Two cards, one featuring a cat and the other a dog (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade cards, N.B. Pratt and Company, 188-?; Two copies of card depicting a girl feeding tea to a Newfoundland dog (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, N.B. Pratt and Company, 188-?; Two different designs each featuring a woman surrounded by patchwork (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, N.B. Pratt and Company, 188-?; Back of card lists other Hartford businesses (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, D.K. Prescott, 188-?; Two different designs featuring a boy and girl playing outdoors (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, Preston and Kenyon, 190-?; "We use and recommend the Paints manufactured by the Acme White Lead and Color Works, Detroit, Mich." (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Trade card, Preston and Kenyon, 189-?; Printed by A. W. Lang, Steam Printer, 96 Asylum. (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Business card, Project Image, 198-?; Business card of Charlotte Berman, Director (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Postcard, Puritan Laundry, 191-?; "Gentlemen! We beg to announce that we are doing high grade collar and shirt work." (Box 10, Folder P)
  - Business card, David F. Ransom, 191-? (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Postcard, J.G. Rathbun and Company, 187-?; "Smoke Manhatta. The Finest 5c. Cigar in the Market." (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Trade card, J.G. Rathbun and Company, 187-?; Four different designs featuring baseball players. (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Trade card, J. Wilkie Reid, 188-?; "Balls costumed in or out of the City. Costumes sent anywhere C.O.D." (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Trade card, C.E. Rhodes and Company, 18--?; Design features Indians hunting gazelles with leopards. (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Postcard, M.H. Rhodes, Inc., 1943; "Watch for the most important idea yet developed in the Parking Meter business." (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Business card, Rivard Opticians, 198-?; Business cards of Rene F. Rivard and Janet Rivard Sheltz (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Trade card, William W. Roberts, 185-? (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Trade card, Roberts' Opera House, 1882; "Bennett & Moulton's Comic Opera Company… will present the following Operas… " (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Trade card, Roberts' Opera House, 1882; Four different designs featuring cats. "First Annual Celebration of the present management." (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Label, Robbins and Winship, 185-?; Manuscript note: "Daniel W. Norton, Suffield, Conn. / Please Return Matting." (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Trade card, Rodgers, 188-?; Two different designs (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Trade card, Rodgers, 188-?; Two different designs (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Trade card, Rodgers, 188-?; One design featuring a bird and butterfly (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Trade cards, William Rogers Manufacturing Company, 1885; Two copies of card depicting a boy and a girl on roller skates. One copy stamped "Jas. Mooney & Co. / Bangor, Me." (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Postcards, William Rogers Manufacturing Company, 1892; Two postcards with the printed signature of M.D. Munson (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Postcard, William Rogers Manufacturing Company, 1893; One postcard with the printed signature "'THE WM. ROGERS MFG. CO." (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Postcard, William Rogers Manufacturing Company, 189-?; One postcard with the printed signature "J. B. Bemis." (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Trade card, George Rohrmayer, 189-?; "Ladies' and Gents' Garments of Every Description, Dyed and Cleansed." Annie Elty, Winsted, Ct., General Agent. 3 copies of card, one with manuscript notes. (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Trade card, E.M. Rose, 188-?; "Birthday and Fancy Cards a Specialty." (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Business card, Rose Marie Beauty Parlor, 192-?; Wilma D. Benton and Alida O'Shaughnessy, Proprietors (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Postcard, J.S. Round and Company, 190-?; "Watches and Jewelry sold on easy weekly payments." (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Postcard, The Round Table, 196-?; "Dancing Nightly to the Johnny Mastrio Quartet." (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Postcard, Rourke-Eno Paper Company, 192-?; "Your Health First / Vortex-Burt, the perfect Cup." (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Trade card, A.H. Rowe, 189-?; Design features a horse-shoe (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Trade card, Royal Lunch, 19--?; "Eating That’s Our Specialty… Try one of our 20 cent dinners…." "10345 People were served by us in our first year just ended." (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Trade card, A.A. Ruggles, 185-? (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Trade cards, Ryder's Hotel, 1860?; Two copies. Includes price list (Box 10, Folder R)
  - Trade card, W.R. Sage, 18--?; One floral design (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, William G. Saint George, 18--?; Two different designs featuring sea shells. (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, Saint John's Hotel, 185-?; Lester S. Hills, Proprietor. "Renovated, Refitted and Refurnished… Fine Billiard Hall in the House." (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Postcards, J.W. Salzer, 1907; Two postcards postmarked 1907 advertising Welcome Soap and Sunlight Soap (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, J. Samuels and Company, 188-?; Two different designs (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, J. Samuels and Company, 187-?; Design features a girl playing a lute (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Business card, San Juan Center, Inc., 198-?; Business card of Jose A. Maldonado (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, George Saunders and Company, 187-?; Six different floral designs (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Business card, William d. Sauders, 19--? (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, Mrs. E.M. Sawyer, 187-?; Two different floral designs (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, George O. Sawyer, 187-?; Two different cards, each with a map of the United States on the back, one copyrighted 1877, the other copyrighted 1879. (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Business card, G.O. Sawyer and Company, 19--?; Business card of Edith E. Perkins, Cloak Department (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, Ernest Schall, 1878?; "Sole Agent for the Aug. Saltzman Watches." (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade cards, Ernest Schall, 188-?; Four different cards shaped like artists' palettes. Schall's name is virtually illegible. (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, Ernest Schall, 188-?; One design featuring a child with a butterfly net (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, Theo. G. Scheck, 18--? (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, F. Schroeder, 187-?; One floral design (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, Joseph Schwab, 186-?; Address "395 Main Street" is printed on card, but it is stamped "Removed to 333 Main Street, Hills Block." (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, F. Schwengler, 18--? (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Postcard, David Seide, 1908; Postcard features a rebus: "Can You Solve It? Bring us a correct solution… and receive a useful present…" (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, Harvey Seymour, 186-?; Manuscript calculations on back (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, Lincoln Seyms and Company, 192-?; When held to light, cards reveal advertisement for "Union Club Coffee." (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, Shannon and Marwick, 188-?; "For Sore Throat, Blisters, Burns, Wounds, Piles, Inflammation, Neuralgia &c. use Risley's Extract of Witch Hazel." (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Business card, Shoor Brothers, 198-?; Business card of Bill Lear (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, Shoninger and Company, 187-?; One floral design (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, Mrs. S.F. Shove, 188-?; "Opening of Fall Styles, Saturday, Sept. 18th and Monday, Sept. 20th." (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, Sigourney House, 190-?; N[ancy] J. Coyle, Proprietor. Trade card and envelope with return address. (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, H.A. Sillence Co., 193-?; Agent for United Van Service, Inc. (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Brochure, W.G. Simmons Company, Inc., 190-?; Brochure advertising hosiery for men, women, and children (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, T. Sisson and Company., 18--?; "Detroit White Lead Works' Ready-Mixed, Varnish Gloss, Carriage Paints." (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Business card, Skywalk Restaurant, 198-?; Business card of Tony Scacca (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Postcard, Smith and Hegeman, 191-?; Partners are Eddy N. Smith and Arthur W. Hegeman. "We make Post Card Photographs of your hours, yourself, the children, your auto, the cat, the dog, or of any subject you may desire." (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, C. Smith and Company, 18--?; Partners are C. H. Smith and H. R. Hills (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, Robert H. Smith, 188-?; "New Files on Hand and Made to Order." (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade cards, Thomas H. Smith, 1879; "Two different floral cards: "Hot Meals at All Hours 25 Cents." (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, Thomas H. Smith, 1879; "Hot Meals at All Hours 25 Cents." "Formerly Green's Restaurant>" (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, Thomas H. Smith, 188-?; Three different floral designs. A. W. Lang, Printer, Hartford. (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, Thomas H. Smith, 188-?; Three different floral designs. A. W. Lang, Printer, Hartford. (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, Thomas H. Smith, 188-?; One comic design, "Quack Doctor," printed by Bufford, Boston. (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, William B. Smith, 187-? (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, Charles Soby, 189-?; Brands include Hazel Kirke, Blue Ribbon, Seal of Conn., Our Bachelors, Partegas, Old Mill, La Espanola, Sports, LaRosa (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Postcard, Southern new England Grocers Association, 1892; Postcard announcing that meeting has been postponed (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Business card, Spencer's, 198-? (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, Sperry, Bulkley and Pushee, 185-?; "S. B. & P. have a most extensive assortment of Patterns and manufacture to order, at short notice, almost any description of Castings in common use." (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Business card, Standard Builders, 199-?; Business card of Jonathan Moulton, Project Engineer (Box 10, Folder S)
  - Trade card, J.S. Stannard, 188-?; "Always Has the Best!" (Box 10, Folder S)